onlineslangdictionary.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy Policy | The Online Slang Dictionary

Can you believe that a neo-Nazi website gets a million more visitors a month than we do, due to Google's penalty against this site? And a Google employee lied about the penalty. **November update** : I've started naming names. Read the details here. 

Can you believe that a neo-Nazi website gets a million more visitors a month than we do, due to Google's penalty against this site? **And a Google employee lied about it**. But I'm naming names. Read more here. 

There's a neo-Nazi website that gets a million more visitors a month than we do, due to Google's penalty against this site. **And a Google employee lied about it**. Read the details here. 

A neo-Nazi website gets a million more visitors a month than we do, due to Google's penalty against this site. **A Google employee lied about it**. Read more here. 

A neo-Nazi website gets a million more visitors a month than we do, due to Google's penalty against this site. **And Google lied about it**. More here. 

We will never share any personally identifiable information (such as your e-mail address or location) with anyone, unless required to do so by law. See below for more information.

(Our e-mail updates are handled entirely by the Google FeedBurner service. You can view its privacy policy [here](http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/privacy).)

## Website Visitors

Like most websites, The Online Slang Dictionary collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The Online Slang Dictionary's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how The Online Slang Dictionary's visitors use its website. From time to time, The Online Slang Dictionary may release non-personally- identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

The Online Slang Dictionary also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. The Online Slang Dictionary does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally- identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to The Online Slang Dictionary's website choose to interact with The Online Slang Dictionary in ways that require The Online Slang Dictionary to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that The Online Slang Dictionary gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, to register for an account, we ask you to provide an email address. In each case, The Online Slang Dictionary collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with The Online Slang Dictionary. The Online Slang Dictionary does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

The Online Slang Dictionary may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, The Online Slang Dictionary may monitor the most popular pages on the site. The Online Slang Dictionary may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, The Online Slang Dictionary does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

The Online Slang Dictionary discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally- identifying information only if required to do so by law, or when The Online Slang Dictionary believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of The Online Slang Dictionary or third parties. The Online Slang Dictionary will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.  The Online Slang Dictionary takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Online Slang Dictionary uses cookies to help The Online Slang Dictionary identify and track visitors, their usage of The Online Slang Dictionary website, and their website access preferences. The Online Slang Dictionary visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using The Online Slang Dictionary's website, with the drawback that certain features of The Online Slang Dictionary's website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Ads

Because this site uses Google AdSense for advertising.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## FeedBurner

The Online Slang Dictionary uses Google's FeedBurner service to deliver e-mail updates. If you choose to subscribe to email updates, your email address goes directly to Google. You can view the FeedBurner privacy statement [here](http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/privacy).

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, The Online Slang Dictionary may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in The Online Slang Dictionary's sole discretion. The Online Slang Dictionary encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
